♪ [Music] ♪
[Heavy thud]- Ugh!
♪ Chet Rong ♪
Chet Rong here
with the Rong way to do Agile
Today, stand-ups.
First, do you stand-ups sitting down
so that everyone is comfortable.
The more people, the better
so invite the whole office.
Be sure to vary meeting time and places
to keep everyone on their toes.
- Hello?
- Next, pass an object around
and make sure that the object is heavy
so everyone can feel the weight
of what is being said.
Whoever is holding
the object should listen
while everyone else talks.
Talk about whatever you need
for as long as you want.
Discuss any and all issues at length.
[chatter]
These meetings will take up
most of the morning
but you'll still have a few hours
in the afternoon
to get project work done.
[heavy thud]
And that's the Rong way to do stand-ups.
♪ [Music] ♪